checkpageranking.com 2016-02-13

# Privacy Policy | Check Page Rank!

What information do we collect?  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or contact us.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other business related information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

What do we use your information for?  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
; To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)  
; To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)  
; To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)  
; To process transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

; To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.  
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

How do we protect your information?  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

Do we use cookies?  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We use remarketing advertising campaigns to advertise online. This means that once you visit specific pages of our site we consider you part of that product or services audience, and we may place a cookie on your browser to signify that you showed interest in our products or services and to advertise to you in the future for those products or services.

Third-party vendors, including Google, show your ads on sites across the Internet, that may detect that cookie and show you ads related to our Company.

These third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your past visits to our website.

You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Ads Preferences Manager. Alternatively, you can also opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Online Privacy Policy Only  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Terms and Conditions  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://checkpagerank.net/termsandconditions.php

Your Consent  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 12/13/2013

Contacting Us  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.  
http://checkpagerank.net  
980 N Michigan Ave Ste 1400  
Chicago, Illinois 60611  
United States  
info@checkpagerank.net  
1-312-985-7701
